

CRISTIAN ORREGO Systems Engineer

O Cartago Valle del Cauca - Colombia

☐ cristian.duquew@gmail.com

& 311 398 8094

SOCIAL

in @cristianorrego

@cristianorregod

f @cristianorregod

PROFILE

I am a Systems Engineer with more than one year of experience in web development and IT administration. Provide solutions, work on team, leading projects, responsibility and respect for my work are some of the characteristics of my professional life.

EDUCATION

TECHNOLOGIST MECDICE ®

National Learning Service

2014 - 2016

SYSTEMS ENGINEER ®

Remington University Corporation

2018 - 2021

WEB DEVELOPMENT ®

Udemy

2019 - 2021

SKILLS

- Php Php
- Laravel
- Html 5
- Vue W
- Css 3
- MySQL



EXPERIENCE

IT ADMINISTRATOR From 2015 to 2016 | Universidad del Valle

I worked in the institution performing my work with responsibility, helping to improve internet presence of the entity redesigning the website.

IT ADMINISTRATROR

From 2016 to 2019 | La Sucursal Ferreteria

A company where I learned to manage a work team, delegating functions to achieve a common goal, the systematization of processes.

COMPUTER SCIENCE TEACHER

From 2020 to 2021 | Colegio Técnico Comercial Diocesano Santa María

In my work with the institution I have strengthened my knowledge and skills, in addition to learning by teaching, I have managed the institution's internet presence.

CERTIFIED

IT Essentials 🖁

Function of computer components, their assembly and setting.

Version Control System (Git) ♀

Git and Github professional course for version management.

Master in PHP 9

Web development course with the PHP Laravel framework.

REFERENCES

Accountant

Paul Avendaño Poveda

Phone: 318 231-7314

Email: pap8503@hotmail.com

Systems Engineer

Mauricio Montoya Abadía

Phone: 320 671-8515

Email: mmontoyaabadia@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

INTERESTS

①

Football

Photography

Reading

Travel

Music